ibiza-spotlight.com 2019-06-09

# Ibiza Spotlight Privacy Policy | Ibiza Spotlight

Ibiza Spotlight S.L.  
Avenida Dr. Fleming, 35  
San Antonio, Baleares 07820  
España

You may contact us via the following [e-mail account](mailto:gdpr@ibiza-spotlight.com?subject=Data%20Protection%20Enquiry). Or you may call us at +34 971 346671, Monday to Friday, during office hours.

PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION INFO: According to the General Data Protection Regulation (UE) 2016/679, regarding your personal data management, we inform you: Data Controller: IBIZA SPOTLIGHT S.L, Avenida Dr. Fleming Nº35, 07820, Sant Antoni de Portmany(ILLES BALEARS). Purpose: Sending info and answering your questions and inquiries as long our relationship is going on and we have your consent. Lawful basis for processing: Performance of a contract or data subject's consent. Data disclosure. Your personal data will not be disclosed unless forced by law. Rights. You have right of access, right to rectification, right to erasure and data portability, and right to restriction of processing, writing a letter accompanied by a copy of an official document evidencing your identity to the Data Controller. You have also the right to logde a complaint with a Supervisory Authority (Spanish Supervisory Authority is Agencia Española de Protección de Datos). More info. Please visit the legal notice (Aviso Legal) in our website.

### What data do we collect during e-commerce transactions?

We do collect some online contact information (email address) and sometimes the name and address and contact details (telephone, email address) from visitors who purchase club, activity or other tickets or rent a villa.

### What do we use this data for?

This data will only be used during the processing of your order and occasionally to inform you of forthcoming events and products/services which we think may be of interest. This is never more than three times per year. You can opt-out at any time. Clear instructions to unsubscribe are sent with every mailing.

### Newsletter subscriptions

Our newsletter database is opt-in only. You can sign up during the purchase process or elsewhere in our site. We will not add you to our newsletter database without your explicit consent.

### What anonymous data do we collect during your use of this website?

  1. HTTP cookies / Query-string portion of URI
  2. Full IP address
  3. HTTP request method
  4. Data bytes in response
  5. Response status code

This type of information is deemed non-identifiable. This means that there is no reasonable way for the site to identify the individual person this data was collected from. The query string portion of the URI and HTTP Cookies are used to track referrals from Search Engines. Our Web Server collects access logs containing some of this information. We use it for maintaining and improving our website.

**By using our website you agree that we can set cookies and collect the above data for the following purposes:**

  1. Anonymous user analysis.
  2. Web site and system administration.

### Third party tracking

**Google:** We use third-party advertising companies (primarily Google) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Facebook:** On our facebook pages we have created two apps which are loaded within an iframe which contain links back to our site. We do **not** collect any user information within these apps. Your use of Facebook in general and your relationship with Facebook are subject to Facebook's own Privacy Policy and Facebook's other terms and policies, which Ibiza Spotlight S.L. does not control.

### Our policy

**This data will be used only by ourselves.** Ibiza Spotlight will **never** sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

### Dispute resolution

We have the following dispute resolution mechanisms.

Ibiza Spotlight complies with the Organic Law 15/1999 from 13th of December regarding Personal Data Protection, as confirmed by the Spanish Data Protection Agency. All disputes regarding the access to and storing of personal user information will be handled by our office. You may contact us via the following [e-mail account](mailto:gdpr@ibiza-spotlight.com?subject=Data%20Protection%20Enquiry).
